Always like a little sleeping spot.
This is a large sleeping area.
All the footprints
They have the bathroom here, water.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Up, up, up, up. I'll hold you. I'll hold
you. I'll hold you.
Come on. Opa.
There we go. Woo.
Yeah, this is the way.
Do you have a headlamp?
I don't actually.
Oh, wow.
Like a waterfall here when it rains.
Yeah, there's a deer. Lots of deer poo.
Oh, yeah, it's a good cave actually.
It's about
20 m there.
Yeah, it's pretty nice.
Classic secret cave behind the
waterfall. Yeah, exactly there.
What is Is a drop here?
Yeah.
Sunny. Up up up up up up up up up up.
Good boy.
Go go go go go go go go. You can do it.
You can do it. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Go go go.
Excellent boy. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Good boy.
Good boy.
I'll do the zigzag. Go go.
Oh, where were we going that way, boy?
That is not the way.
So, that's the ridge.
That's where we went. Where we go we go,
yeah. Yeah.
Oh, I know where we are.
Oh, there's a bench here.
Oh, it's up over there.
Yeah, that that trail right down there. Go go.
Go go.